Guide to the Jennifer (Sudie) Nostrand Papers MSS.082
Fales Library and Special Collections
Jennifer (Sudie) Nostrand Papers
1963-2021
Fales Library and Special Collections
Nostrand, Sudie
MSS.082
14.26 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 18 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 small case, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 oversize folder in shared housing
40 kilobytes in 1 computer file
Jennifer (Sudie) Nostrand is a New York poet whose work has been published in literary magazines including The California Quarterly, The Greensboro Review, and the Manhattan Poetry Review. Nostrand earned her Ph.D. in English Literature from New York University. The Jennifer (Sudie) Nostrand Papers (1963-2021) largely consist of handwritten and typed daily notes and writings dating from 1963 to 2009; a typed, notated compilation of Nostrand's poetry organized by date from 1965 to 2014; and published copies of Nostrand's poetry from 1965 to 2021, with a selection of correspondence, class notes, and unpublished materials related to the editing, publication, or review of her work.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Jennifer (Sudie) Nostrand between 2000-2024. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2000.082, 2005.082, 2006.082, 2019.020, 2019.034, and 2024.031.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in four series. The contents of each series are arranged chronologically by their publication date, or date of creation for papers. The collection was processed at the folder-level. The series arrangement of the records is as follows:
Series I. Documents
Series II. Printed Materials
Series III. Oversized Materials
Series IV. Data Storage
Biographical Note
Jennifer (Sudie) Nostrand is a New York poet whose work has been published in such literary magazines as The California Quarterly, The Greensboro Review, the Manhattan Poetry Review—among many others.
In 1984, Nostrand released Joan, a piece on the French heroine Joan of Arc, with the Mimeograph Press as part of the St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery's Poetry Project. The March Street Press later published a collection of her works entitled The Paris Poems in 2004 and in 2010 Nostrand released Variations with the same independent publisher. In response to The Paris Poems, American poet, editor, and activist, Ron Kolm claimed that, "Sudie Nostrand has that very rare ability to make the spiritual manifest (The Paris Poems)."
Nostrand earned a Ph.D. in English Literature from New York University. In addition to her published work, Nostrand participated in various public readings in New York City. She has gone by various names throughout her career: Jennifer Nostrand, Jennifer Sudie Nostrand, S. Nostrand, and, simply, Sudie.
Sources: Nostrand, Sudie."Biography." Variations, Greensboro, North Carolina: March Street Press, 2010. Nostrand, Sudie. The Paris Poems, Greensboro, North Carolina: March Street Press, 2004.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Scope and Contents
The Jennifer (Sudie) Nostrand Papers (1963-2021) contains material created and collected by poet Sudie Nostrand. The collection includes handwritten and typed daily notes and writings dating from 1963 to 2009; a notated compilation of Nostrand's poetry organized by date from 1965 to 2014; and published copies of Nostrand's poetry from 1965 to 2021. The collection also includes correspondence, class notes, and unpublished materials related to the editing, publication, or review of her work.
American poetry -- 20th century -- Periodicals; Poets -- United States.; American poetry -- 20th century.; American poetry -- New York (State) -- New York; Nostrand, Sudie; St. Mark's Church In-the-Bowery (New York, N.Y.). Poetry Project; Claire, William F.
- Series I: Documents, 1963-2018
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains material related to Sudie Nostrand's writing including handwritten and typed daily notes and writings dating from 1963 to 2009 which contain writing ideas, selections of her poetry, and diary-type entries on events and activities. A typed, notated compilation of Nostrand's poetry is organized by date from 1965 to 2014. This series also contains proofs and correspondence related to her 2004 book The Paris Poems as well as a master copy for her 2010 book Variations. Posters, flyers, listings, reviews, a bibliography, and correspondence with fellow-poet William Claire, and also with various journals and publications regarding submissions of her work is also in this series.
  - Daily Writings / Notes, 1963 - July 1971 (Box 13, Folder 3-5, Box 14, Folder 1-5, Box 15, Folder 1-6)
  - Daily Writings / Notes, July 1971 - May 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1-5, Box 17, Box 18, Folder 1-4)
  - Daily Writings / Notes, June 1992 - 2009 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
  - Bibliography For Sudie Nostrand, 1965-2013 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bibliography - 2 Hard Copies, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chronologically Grouped Poetry -- Typed, Edited, 1965-2014 (Box 12, Folder 1-5, Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Typed Writings / Notes, 1966 - May 1982 (Box 19, Folder 4-5, Box 20, Folder 1-5, Box 21, Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Typed Writings / Notes -- "A Portrait of Washington Square" Project, October 13, 1981 - October 13, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Typed Writings / Notes, May 1982 - 2009 (Box 22, Folder 3-5, Box 23, Folder 1-6, Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- William Claire, 1977-2015 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence -- Publications and Journal Submission-Related, 1980-2018 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- David Cole, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acceptance Letter from White Pelican Review, April 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Posters, Flyers, Listings, Reviews, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Files, Bibliography, and Poems by Nostrand, 2001; undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Paris Poems -- Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Paris Poems -- Proofs, Feburary 25, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Paris Poems -- Proofs, April 9, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Paris Poems -- Proofs, April 27, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Paris Poems -- Proof, November 12, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Paris Poems -- Proofs, November 26, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Variations -- Master Copy, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Class Notebook -- Vienamese Poetry, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Series II: Printed Materials, 1965-2021, undated
  This series is comprised of original publications featuring Nostrand's writings from 1965-2021.
  - List of Published Works, circa 2018 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "One" in The Angels..., Summer 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "For Words" in Writer's Notes & Quotes (vol. 14 no. 4), September 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Seen From A Rock" in The Angels (vol. 2 no. 7), Winter 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Untitled" in Driftwood East, Winter 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "The Land..." in Indigo (vol. 2 no. 3), March 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Untitled" in Driftwood East (vol. 3 no. 3), Summer 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Untitled" in Driftwood East, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Untitled" in Rendezous with the Sea, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "With Rapid Smile He Said" in Mississippi Review (vol. 5 no. 2), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Two Poems in The Conneticut Magazine (vol.4 no. 1), Spring 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Untitled" in Bardic Echoes (vol. 17 no. 2), June 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Untitled" in Bardic Echoes (vol. 17 no. 3), September 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Untitled" in Bardic Echoes (vol. 17 no. 4), December 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Two Poems in Modus Operandi (vol. 8 no. 6), June 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Two Poems in Sulphur River Review (vol. 13 no. 2), September 22, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "Untitled" in Phantasm (vol. 2 no. 5), September - October 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Untitled" in The Spoon River Quarterly (vol. 3 no. 1), Winter 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Untitled" in Cambic Poetry Project (no.1), November 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Untitled" in Kansas Quarterly (vol. 11 no.3), Summer 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Least Expected Comes the Rush" in Kansas Quarterly (Vol. 11, No. 3), Summer 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Two Poems in the Gramercy Review (vol. 13 no. 4; vol. 4 no. 1), 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "Untitled" in Grub Street (no. 10), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "Diana Wades Still Water," and "Antigone" in The Gramercy Review (Vol. 4, No. 1), Winter 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "There can Only Be More" in Green's Magazine (vol. 8 no. 4), Summer 1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "There Can Only Be More" in Green's Magazine, 8 (No. 4), Summer 1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Two Poems in Words, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Cleopatra" in Phil Honey It's Time We Settled Down, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Two Poems in Phil Honey, It's Time We Settled Down, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "I Would Have Thought" in The Hoboken Terminal (vol. 1 no. 2), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - "Letter to Henry VIII" in Public Illumination Magazine (no.19), February 1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "Untitled" in Arulo (vol. 21), December 1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Two Poems in Footwork, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - "Be Sculptor to Memory" in The Altadena Review (No. 6), Spring 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Three Poems in Telephone (no. 18), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "You Stand" in The Hoboken Terminal (vol. 2 no. 1), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Three Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 9), Winter 1983 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "Untitled" in Arulo (vol. 22), February 1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - "Untitled" in The Altadena Review (no.6), Spring 1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Three Poems in New Leaves Review (vol. 1 no. 6), Spring 1983 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - "You Are Silent and Compact" in Arulo! (vol. 23), April 1983 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Three Poems in New Leaves (no. 7), Summer 1983 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Three Poems in New Leaves (no. 8), Fall 1983 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - "We Sit Here" in The Hoboken Terminal (vol. 3 no.1), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Three Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 11), Summer 1984 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Three Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 12), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Three Poems in Amelia (vol. 2 no. 1), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Untitled" in Cuttings: a Collection of Short Poems Selected from New Leaves Review, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Two Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 13), Spring 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Tree in the Orchard,"... in Amelia (No. 1), April 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Two Poems in New Leaves Review 14, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Untitled ("October Fills the Park") in Amelia (vol. 2 no. 2), October 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "October Fills the Park" in Amelia, 2 (No. 2), October 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Two Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 17), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "How Easy the Sun Comes" in The Kindred Spirit (no. 10), Winter 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "It Could Be Sunday Afternoon" in Embers (Vol. 11, No. 1), Spring/Summer 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "The Silver Dressing Table Set," and "In a House by a River" in Amelia, 3 (No. 1), January 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Two Poems in Amelia (vol. 3 no. 1), January 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Untitled ( "It Could be Sunday Afternoon") in Embers: A Collection (vol. 11 no. 1), Spring/Summer 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Two Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 15), Spring/Summer 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Two Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 16), Summer (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Cleopatra" in Jean's Journal (vol. 23 no. 4), December 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Untitled" in The Louisville Review (no. 21, 22), Fall 1986 - Spring 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Three Poems in Amelia (vol. 4 no. 3), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Two Poems in New Leaves Review (no. 18), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "You Pick Me Up in a Cab,"... in Amelia, 4 (No. 3), 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Poem" in New Leaves Review 19, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Two Poems in Amelia (vol. 5, no. 2), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Two Poems in Appearances (no. 14), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "The Traffic Stops," and "Those Two Men" in Amelia, 13 (Vol. 5, No. 2), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Two Poems in Parting Gifts (vol.1, no.1), Summer 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "I Wonder What You Think" in Z Miscellaneous (vol. 2 no. 3), May 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "The Traffic Stops," and "In Large Cities" in Parting Gifts (No. 1), Summer 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "The Army of Angels" in Parting Gifts (Vol. 1, No. 2), Winter 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Four Poems in Orphic Lute (vol. 38 no. 2), Summer 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "Untitled" in Parting Gifts (vol. 1 no. 2), Winter 1988 - 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "Hunting Scenes at the Carlyle" in Kansas Quarterly (vol. 21 no. 3), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "Hunting Scenes at the Carlyle" in Kansas Quarterly (vol. 21 no. 3), Summer 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - "Hunting Scenes at the Carlyle" in Kansas Quarterly (Vol. 21, No, 3), Summer 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - "Untitled" in Blue Unicorn (vol. 13 no. 1), October 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - "Untitled" ("In the Cool and Rainy Evening...") in The MacGuffin: The New Formalism in Poetry (vol. 7 no. 2), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - "We Sit by the Fire" in The Pacific Review, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - "We Sit by the Fire" in The Pacific Review (Vol. 8), 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "In the Cool and Rainy Evening" in The MacGuffin (Vol. 7, No. 11), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - "Untitled" ("His Plane Left this Morning...") in Untitled (ed. Larry Oberc), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - "Untitled" in The MacGuffin (vol. 7 no. 3), Fall 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - "We Had Lunch in a Utrillo" in The MacGuffin (Vol. 7, No. 3), Fall 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Two Poems in the Ledge (vol. 2 no. 3), November 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "This 1868 Painting,"... in Color Wheel (No. 2), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Untitled" in Kumquat Meringue (no. 3), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Untitled" ("The Filmy Curtains...") in Parnassus Literary Journal (vol. 16 no. 1), Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Four Poems in Sisyphus (vol. 3 no. 1), Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - "Luxembourg Gardens" in The Greensboro Review (no. 52), Summer 1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - "Untitled" in The Bridge (vol. 2 no. 2), Summer 1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Four Poems in Color Wheel (no. 2), Midsummer/Autumn Equinox 1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - "You Died" in The Bridge (Vol. 2, No. 2), Summer 1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Luxembourg Gardens" in The Greensboro Review (No. 52), Summer 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "In the Cool and Rainy Evening" in In the West of Ireland, Autumn 1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Four Poems in The Color Wheel Reader, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Two Poems in Birmingham Poetry Review (no. 10), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - "Untitled" in Amelia (vol. 7 no. 2) x2, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "The Pigeon Woman" in Soundings East, Spring/Summer 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "Untitled" in Parnasus Literary Journal (vol. 17 no. 3), Fall 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "In the Cool and Rainy Evening" in Amelia, 21 (Vol. 7, No. 2), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Three Poems in Color Wheel (no. 8), Autumn Equinox 1993 - Candlemas 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Untitled" ("In the Cool and Rainy Evening...") in The Galley Sail Review (vol. 13 no. 2 issue 43), Fall 1993 - Winter 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "In the Cool and Rainy Evening" in The Galley Sail Review (Vol. 13, No. 2, Issue 43), Fall 1993- Winter 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Three Poems in The Hiram Review (no. 55/56), Fall 1993 - Summer 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "We Had Lunch in a Utrillo" ... in The Hiram Poetry Review (No. 55/56), Fall 1993 - Summer 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Catherine Blake's Husband," ... in River Oak Review (No. 3), Fall 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Three Poems in River Oak Review, Fall 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "The Stone Girls in the Louvre," "Once a Queen Slept,"... in Birmingham Poetry Review (No. 13), Fall/Winter 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Two Poems in Pacific Coast Journal (vol. 3 no. 3), Summer 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Five Poems in Birmingham Poetry Review (no. 13), Fall-Winter 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "It wasn't As If I'd Come" in Slant: A Journal of Poetry (no. 10), Summer 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Indexed in Birmingham Poetry Review (no. 15), Fall - Winter 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "They wave" in the Bridge (vol. 5 no. 2), Winter 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "They Wave from the Station Platform" in The Bridge (Vol. 4, No. 2), Winter 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "As You Nap I Take a Walk" in The Green Hills Literary Lantern (no. 7), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "That Bird in the tree" in Connecticut River Review, Winter/Spring 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Cars Line Up in Front" in Wings (vol. 6 no. 2), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "Luxembourg Gardens" in Black River Review, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "Cars Line Up in Front" in Wings Magazine, Inc. (Vol. 6, No. 2), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "In the Bus Taking Us" in Sulphur River Literary Review (Vol. 13, No. 2), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Untitled" in Oxymoron (Vol. 1), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Untitled" in Oxymoron (vol.1), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Untitled" in Oxymoron (vol. 2), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Two Poems in Parting Gifts (vol. 10 no. 2), Winter 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Magic" in Bless the Day: Prayers & Poems to Nurture Your Soul, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "Untitled" in The Unbearables Assembling Magazine Carnaval All the Time! (no. 8), June 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Untitled" in Pearl (no. 27), Fall/Winter 1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Three Poems in Sarasota Review of Poetry (vol. 3), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Those Two Men" in Cumberland Poetry Review (vol. 19 no. 1), Fall 1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "You Are the Moment" in California Quarterly (vol. 26 no. 3), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Three Poems in Sarasota Review (no. 1), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "They're Restoring the Ceiling" in The Bridge (vol. 7 no. 2), Winter 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Two Poems in Roanke Review (vol. 26 no. 1), Spring 2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Untitled" in White Pelican Review (vol. 1 no. 1), Spring 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "It's Been Two Days" in Potpourri (vol. 13 no. 1), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "He and His Wife..." in Birmingham Poetry Review (No. 24), Spring/Summer 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Untitled" in Birmingham Poetry Review, Spring - Summer 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Untitled" in Illay's Honey (vol. 7 no. 2), Summer 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "It wasn't as if I'd Come..." in California Quarterly (vol. 27 no. 4), Fall 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Indexed in Birmingham Poetry Review (no. 25), Spring/Summer 2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Three Poems in Wavelength: A Magazine of Poetry (no. 5), Summer 2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Untitled" in Simple Joys: A Reminder to Slow Down and Enjoy the Little Things in Life, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Untitled" in California Quarterly (vol. 29 no. 2), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "Eagles" in The Mid-America Poetry Review (vol. 4 no. 2) x2, Summer - Autumn 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Hunting Scenes at the Carlyle" in Cumberland Poetry Review (vol. 23 no. 1), Fall 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "Untitled" in Hidden Oak, Fall/Winter 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Two Poems in "The Green Hills Literary Latern" (no. 15), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "I'm Coming Back" in North American Review (vol. 289 no. 2), March/April 2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Two Poems in Birmingham Poetry Review (no. 28), Winter/Spring 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "The Young Couple in a Picture Album" in The Mid-American Poetry Review (vol. 5 no. 1), Spring 2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Indexed in the Mid-America Poetry Review (vol. 5 no. 3), 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - "Untitled" in Spire, Spring 2005 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "We Were Figures in Silver" in The Green Hills Literary Lantern (vol. 16), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Two Poems in Everyday Blessings 2006: A Year of Inspiration, Comfort and Gratitude, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "Hunting Scenes at the Carlyle" in Plainsongs (vol. 26 no. 3), Spring 2006 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Two Poems in The Alembic, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - "Untitled" in California Quarterly (vol. 32 no. 1), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Grandpa Slowly Glides His Boat" in Karamu (vol. 20 no. 2), Spring 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Untitled" in Bryant Literary Review (no. 8), 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - "Untitled" in Poetry International (no. 18), 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "Untitled" in California Quarterly (vol. 38 no. 1 & 2), 2012 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Untitled" in Birmingham Poetry Review, Spring 2012 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Eagles Fly Over Us" in California Quarterly (vol. 39 no. 2), 2013 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "This 1868 Painting" in (vol. 33 no. 3), Spring 2013 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Two Poems in Renegade the Magazine (Winter Issue), Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "Untitled" ("Your Hair is Lightened...") in Phoenix (vol. 7 no. 1), Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "The New York Public Library" in Manhattan Poetry Review (no. 13), Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Poet Lore, 2014-2016 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
  - Plainsongs, 2013-2017 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
  - California Quarterly, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - The Listening Eye, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Listening Eye, 2016-2021 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Poem, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Slant, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - California Quarterly, 2017 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Iconoclast, 2017 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Mudfish 20, 2018 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Passager, 2018 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Blue Unicorn, 2018-2019 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Illuminations, 2018-2020 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Poem, 2018-2020 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Plainsongs, 2019 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Willow Review, 2020 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Talking River Review, 2021 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - The Midwest Review, 2021 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Series III: Oversized Materials, 1982-1988
  Scope and Content
  This series includes print materials, such as oversized publications, which are too large to be stored in record cartons.
  - The Villager (vol. 50 no. 29), July 15, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Listed in NYC Poetry Calendar, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "Untitled" in Timeless Light (MC:VI), January 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "You Open the Rusted Lock" in The Albany Review (vol. 2 no. 8), September 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4, Box Shared Fales 017, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Data Storage, 2001-2005, undated; Prior to 2019, it was documented that the collection included two floppy disks, yet it remains unknown as to the physical location of or the exact media types of these items. It is assumed that these two floppy disks are situated within files in the collection boxes. As of 2019, there were two 3.5" floppy disks incorporated into the collection from accession 2019.020, which were removed using a Digital Media Separation Sheet and have been transferred to the shared container "Born-Digital (Separated from ACCNS)" located on the work shelves at the 20 Cooper Square offsite facility.
  This series includes electronic files which include Nostrand's bibliography dated January 2005, and other unpublished writings from 2001.
  - Nostrand's Bibliography, January 2005; FA_MSS_082_ER_1